{
    "subject": "resource/Mark_Miloscia",
    "predicate": "ontology/militaryBranch",
    "object": "resource/United_States_Air_Force",
    "human_readable": "Mark Miloscia served in the United States Air Force.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9729675650596619,
            "question": "What was Mark Miloscia's role in the United States Air Force?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9454938769340515,
            "question": "What years did Mark Miloscia serve in the United States Air Force?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9324499368667603,
            "question": "Where was Mark Miloscia stationed during his time in the US Air Force?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8139346837997437,
            "question": "How did Mark Miloscia's experience in the US Air Force shape his life after service?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8026494979858398,
            "question": "In what branch of the military did Mark Miloscia serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.78505939245224,
            "question": "Was Mark Miloscia a member of any other branches of the US military?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5899600386619568,
            "question": "Are there any notable events or missions that Mark Miloscia participated in during his service?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5686078071594238,
            "question": "Can you provide details about Mark Miloscia's specific duties during his service?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5043426752090454,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges Mark Miloscia may have faced while serving?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29249751567840576,
            "question": "Did Mark Miloscia receive any awards or honors for his service?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mark Miloscia served in the United States Air Force.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6487_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the challenges Mark Miloscia may have faced while serving?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6487_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide details about Mark Miloscia's specific duties during his service?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6487_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable events or missions that Mark Miloscia participated in during his service?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6487_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6487_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that, according to the documents, Mark Miloscia served as an Air Force officer and a B-52 pilot and contract manager for 10 years (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6487/re-ranker-msmarco/28.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports Mark Miloscia's service in the United States Air Force, mentioning his roles as an Air Force officer, a B-52 pilot, and a contract manager for 10 years."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}